destinationtips.com 2017-09-19

# Privacy Policy - Destination Tips

## Privacy

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

## 1\. Log Files

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol address (IP)
  * Type of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referrring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

## 2\. Cookies

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site. You should review the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers, including Google, for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

## 3\. Others

You may give us personal information about you, such as your name, your contact email and other contact details on various places. This privacy policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

## How and Where We Collect Personal Information:

  * Email
  * Contact Form
  * Blog Comments
  * Subscription for Newsletter

## How We Use Your Personal Information:

The information you give us is absolute safe with us. We will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. But we will never rent, sell, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties.
